https://neo-archaic.ie/cookie-policy/

Skip to Navigation
Cookies and your privacyNeo-Archaic Web Design will not collect any personal information about you on this website without your permission. Any personal information supplied will be treated as confidential and will not be passed to third parties.Technical details of your visit to this website are recorded only for business purposes. These details include IP addresses and web search terms. This information will only be used for statistical and administrative purposes.This privacy policy does not cover any links within this site linking to other sites.Our use of cookiesOur website uses cookies – small text files that are placed on your machine to help the site provide a better user experience. In general, cookies are used to retain user preferences, store information for things like shopping carts, and provide anonymised tracking data to third party applications like Google Analytics. As a rule, cookies will make your browsing experience better. However, you may prefer to disable cookies on this site and on others. The most effective way to do this is to disable cookies in your browser. We suggest consulting the Help section of your browser or taking a look at the About Cookies website which offers guidance for all modern browsersGranting us permission to use cookiesIf the settings on your software that you are using to view this website (your browser) are adjusted to accept cookies we take this, and your continued use of our website, to mean that you are fine with this.Website function cookiesWe use cookies to allow comments on our site and also for enhanced security measures.There is no way to prevent these cookies being set other than to not use our site.Anonymous visitor statistics cookiesThis website uses Google Analytics to help analyse how users use the site. This analytical tool uses cookies to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information in an anonymous form. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity.We will not use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any personally identifiable information of visitors to our site. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any personally identifying information from any source as part of our use of the Google statistical analytics tool. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google, and will not will link, or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a computer user.Our contact form uses Google’s Recaptcha service for spam control, with the same privacy policy as above.This site is protected by reCAPTCHA and the Google Privacy Policy and Terms of Service apply. +353-1-2943946 Karina on LinkedIn Martin on LinkedIn
GET IN TOUCH
KEEP UPDATED
MAIN MENU© 2017 Neo-Archaic | Cookies & PrivacyHomeAbout UsServicesOur WorkOur ClientsBlogContact
HomeAbout UsServicesOur WorkOur ClientsBlogContact
Search for:
+353-1-2943946
Contact
CloseProject
Get in touch
Ask Us Anything!
Your Name Email Phone Number Your Message This site is protected by reCAPTCHA and the Google Privacy Policy and Terms of Service apply.Neo-Archaic
Web Designinfo@neo-archaic.ie +353-1-2943946 Karina on LinkedIn Martin on LinkedInKeep Updated
Subscribe to our monthly mailing list to stay up to date with the latest news, articles, and tips:
Your Email *
Loading...
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website.OkRead more
